Guide to the Duke Ellington School of the Arts collection, 1966-2014 MS2329
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Theatre material, 1971-2000; Series 3
  - Script - Eden: Male Monologue, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Script - Eden: Female Monologue, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Script - Five on the Black Hand Side (1/2), n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Script - Five on the Black Hand Side (2/2), n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Script - The Four Muses, 1981; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Script - Garvey, 1979; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Script - Getting it Together, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Script - Goree Crossing, 1990-1996; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Script - The Great MaDaddy, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Script - Happy Ending, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Script - Harlem Renaissance, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Script - Harriet Tubman Loved Somebody, 1994; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Script - Homegirl, 1998; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Script - Imamu, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Script - In Rhythm and Blues, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Script - Invisible But I'm Somebody, 1975-1976; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Script - Ironhead, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Script - It's a Hardbop Life, 2001; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Script - Jelly's Last Jam (1/2), n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Script - Jelly's Last Jam (2/2), n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Script - Just for Fun My Dears, 1974; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Script - Journey to Tomoroww's World, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Script - King Cotton and the Jiving Cotton Pickers, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Script - Knives (1/2), ca. 1976; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Script - Knives (2/2), ca. 1976; Series 3 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Script - Knock-Knock, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Script - Konvergence, 1977; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Script - Lady Day at Emerson's Bar and Grill, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Script - The Last Forest Fire, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Script - The Legacy, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Script - Look Back in Anger, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Script - Macbeth, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Script - Malindy's Song, 1995; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Script - Mattie and Her Sweetman, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Script - Memories O' Memories, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Script - The Minstrel Boy, 1984; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Script - Miss Ann Don't Cry No More (1/2), 1976; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Script - Miss Ann Don't Cry No More (2/2), 1976; Series 3 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Script - Miss Reardon, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Script - Morning, Noon, and Night, ca. 1970; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Script - Mrs. Patterson, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Script - Nevis Mountain, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Script - The New Cotton Club Revue, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Script - New Orleans Congo Square, 1995; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Script - Noah Muno, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Script - Oh Oh Freedom (1/2), 1975; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Script - Oh Oh Freedom (2/2), 1975; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Script - On Golden Pond, 1979; Series 3 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Script - Open the Backdoor, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Script - Orin, 1971; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Script - The Owl Killer (1/2), n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Script - The Owl Killer (2/2), n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Script - The River Niger (1/2), n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Script - The River Niger (2/2), n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Script - Sands of Time, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Script - Script Side, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Script - Shades of Postal Blue, 1994; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Script - Signs of Life, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Script - Slow Dance on the Killing Ground, ca. 1990s; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Script - Swing/Slide, 1975; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Script - Trees of Eden, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Script - Two Years No Fears, 1974; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Script - Unknown Play, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Script - The Way to Success, 1989; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Script - The Weekend, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Script File Cross Index, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 37)
  - Script File Procedures Memo, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Sheet Music, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Sound, 1988; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Standard Responsibilities, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Synopsis - Bad Man, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Synopsis - The Climax of Your Squeal, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Synopsis - Crosses, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Synopsis - The Hourglass, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Synopsis - Sojourner's Journey, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Synopsis - 'Sty of the Blind Pig, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Synopsis - Undertow, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Technical Theater, 1988; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Technical Personnel, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Technicians - Bailey, Anthony, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Technicians - Candas, Barnes I.: Stage Manager, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Technicians - Chavis, Debi: Stage Manager, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Technicians - Davies, John, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Technicians - Davis, Martin: Sound Designer, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Technicians - Eaton, Edward Joseph, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Technicians - Fleming, Craig S., 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Technicians - Hicks, Beverly: Stage Manager, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Technicians - List of Tech's at a Glance, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Technicians - Morris, Michael, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Technicians - Person, Jimmy, 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Technicians - Pettiste, Bill, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Technicians - Sellers, V. Hana: Light/Sound Designer, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Technicians - Simmons, James E., 1984; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Technicians - Youstra, Bill, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Theater Equpiment - Purchase Orders, 1988; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Theater Maintenance - Purchase Orders, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Theater Materials - Rentals, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Theater Repairs - Purchase Orders, 1988; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Theater Supplies - Purchase Orders, 1987-1988; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Vocal Selections for Diction, n.d., undated; Series 3 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Arts organizations, 1969-2001; Series 4
  This series contains material related to various arts organizations throughout the nation, with the majority relating to Washington, D.C. based arts organizations. It includes articles, reviews, programs, flyers, correspondence, contracts, scripts, and publications. Dates covered include 1969-2001.
  - Articles about Various Arts Organizations (1/2), 1971-2001; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Articles about Various Arts Organizations (2/2), 1971-2001; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Arts Media Service (AMS), 1983; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Bal Masque Event Material, 1982-1983; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Black American Theater: Releases, 1971-1972; Series 4 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Calendars and Schedules, 1969-1985; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - The Colored Museum, 1985-1988; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Contracts, 1975-1998; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1973, 1988; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Dance Visions, 1986-1987; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - D.C. Art Works, 1982, 1988; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - D.C. Black Repertory Company, 1972-1979; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Draculaba d'Haiti, 1983; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Drafts and Mock-Ups, n.d., undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Expo Systems, n.d., undated; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Gap Magazine Material (1/2), 1982; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Gap Magazine Material (2/2), 1982-1983; Series 4 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Greater Washington Cherry Blossom Festival Committe, Inc., 1988; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Flyers and Programs - Various, 1971-1994; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Jazz Freedom Concert, 1986-1987; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - The National Chicano Dance Theatre, n.d., undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - National Lyric Opera Company, n.d., undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Organization Information and Bios, 1981-1982; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Publications - Anthologies, Poetry, and Others, n.d., undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Resumes, n.d., undated; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Shaw College, 1983; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Spunk - Reviews, 1993; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Tams-Witmark Music Library, Inc., 1988-1990; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Theater Sports, 1987; Series 4 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Duke Ellington School of the Arts, 1975-2014; Series 5
  Arranged alphabetically.
  This series contains material related to the Duke Ellington School of the Arts. It includes class lists, syllabi, programs and flyers, newspaper clippings, and event information. Dates covered include 1975-2014.
  - Boxed set of Dance stationary, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Class Lists 1975-1979, Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Classes of 1980-1981, Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Classes of 1983-1984, Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Classes of 1985-1986, Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Class of 1990, Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Class of 1991, Series 5 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Class of 1992, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Class of 1993, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1994, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Class of 1995, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Class of 1996, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Class of 1997, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Class of 1998, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Class of 1999, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Class of 2000, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Class of 2001, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Class of 2002, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Class of 2003, Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Program, 1986; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1988-1991; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Dance Department Annual Spring Concert, 2002; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Grades - Advisory I, 2011-2012; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Grades - Advisory III, 2012; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Jazz Freedom Concert Program, 1987; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Newspaper Clippings and Articles, 1994-1999; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Programs and Flyers, 1977-2009; Series 5 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Senior Prom Picture, 1985; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Schick, James, 2014; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Various, 2008-2009; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Ballet I, 2009-2010; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Ballet I Vocab, 2010; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Ballet II, 2009; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Ballet II Vocab, 1999-2000; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Ballet III/IV, 2009; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Dance History, 2010-2013; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Dance Orientation, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Technique I, 2009; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Technique II, 2009; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Ethnic I, 2009; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Ethnic II, 2009; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Improv, 2013; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Latin Social Dance I, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Modern I, 2009; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Modern II, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Modern III/IV, 2008-2012; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Physical Education, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Syllabi Dance Department - Tap I and II, n.d., undated; Series 5 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Syllabus Over-View, 2012-2013; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Thirty-seventh Commencement Program, 2012; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Three Mo' Tenor's Program, 2013; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Western-Ellington Alumni Magazine, 1991; Series 5 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Audio and visual materials, 1966-2003; Series 6
  Series: Organized into four subseries: Videocassettes, Audio, Photographs, Slides
  This series includes videocassettes, audio, photographs, and slides related to the Duke Ellington School and various functions at the school including graduation, performances, assignments, and trips. Dates covered include 1966-2003.
  - Videocassettes and DVD, 1983-2003; Series 6 Subseries 1
    Subseries: Arranged alphabetically.
    This subseries includes videocassettes of school functions and Anthony Nash Documentary footage. It also contains various small unmarked camcorder tapes. Dates covered include 1983-2003.
    - Anthony Nash Documentary Footage, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 34)
    - Anthony Nash Documentary Footage and school functions, 1997; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 35)
    - School functions (1/2), 1983-1992; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 32)
    - School functions (2/2), 1993-2003; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 33)
    - Various small camcorder tapes, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 36)
    - Where Eagles Fly - DVD, 1995; Series 6 Subseries 1 (Box 47, Folder 21, Dvd data_value_missing_f3c0c2dd9cecb6bc30ecb9cf0a451030, Dvd data_value_missing_4d8079d61ca3b1fa3f1c055873639e1e)
  - Audio, undated; Series 6 Subseries 2
    - Various audio reels, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 37)
      This subseries contains various unmarked audio reels and cassettes.
    - Various sizes of audio cassettes, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 2 (Box 36)
  - Photographs, 1982-2001; Series 6 Subseries 3
    This subseries contains various photographs and negatives of performances. It also includes photographs of dance and theatre performances. Dates covered include 1982-2001.
    - Children's Theater Performance, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - D.C. Black Repertory Company, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Headshots for Various Actors, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - "Imamu" Performance - D.C. Black Repertory Company, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Kodak Picture Disk, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 47, Folder 22, Disk data_value_missing_200f3c9ddd07751eed531cf108dfc4de)
    - Matted and Framed Photographs, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 38)
    - Negatives: Period 4-Photojournalism Joyner, Lakisha 2000-01, 2000-2001; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Out-Of-Area Inactive Members, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Rolled Negative [Leigh Mosley/Kyna] - F, 1989?; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Rolled Negative [Mosley/Angela], 1988?; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Rolled Negative [Mosley/Angela], 1988?; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Various Photographs, 1985-1989; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Various Photographs, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Various Photographs, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Various Photographs of Dancers and Actors, 1982; Series 6 Subseries 3 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Slides, 1966-1996; Series 6 Subseries 4
    There are many files labeled "Slides" each of which represents a set of slides that were in an unmarked container. Those files labeled "Slides" followed by a name in brackets each represent a set of slides that were unmarked aside from the name of the person on the container or on the slides themselves.
    This subseries contains slides related to assignments, trips, and events, as well as various miscellaneous slides. Dates covered include 1966-1996.
    - Angela Bell Photojournalism Ms. Mosley, 1989; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - Annie Watkins Pogo, 1978; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - Assignment #1 John Seder B-, Tanzy Brown B-, 17 April 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - Barrington/200, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Basketball on Farm, Crystal in Wheelbarrow, Adrienne and Clara watching/holding Crystal, September 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - B.B. with headwrap, Leigh with F2 and motor, snowman, baby in carriage, winter scenes, March 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - B.B. Shots with motion in front of wall hanging rug, rear end, Fall 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - B.B., Tina, Me, Penn Center Students; Surroundings, Apt., March 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Bears, Tigers Penn Center Students Picnic, A, August 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Betty Carter, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Betty Carter at Anacostia Park, August 1977; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Betty Carter at Anacostia Park with John Hicks-Piama, August 1977; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Betty Carter Tungsten #2, 18 March 1977; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Black History Program [Leigh Mosley], February 1991; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Carlos Barrington Ass. #1 C/C-, 1987-1995; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Chamber Lain, 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Charlotte Hays, January 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 18)
    - Clement Wells, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 19)
    - Clement Wells #3 - Strobe 400+ ASE 400 8/A Filter Bowser Fill, 1979; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 20)
    - Columbia Scholastic NYC Trip #2, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 21)
    - Copy Work Rejects, 1 April 1980; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 40, Folder 22)
    - Dance Dept. Coleen Deuhurst, Geralyn Gilstrap, 14 June 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - D.D. and Christian for Marys Kays Washingtonian AD, January 1980; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Denise Oliver, 1989; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Deo Kirn Karn and Yogi Giana 232-0059, 2 April 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Derrick Adams, February 1992; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Donyelle Marshall Dance Deparment, 31 October 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Donyelle Marshall Dance Department 00/31 A - Rejects, 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Donyelle Marshall - Harper's Ferry/Farm, October 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Doris Parker Theatre Dept. Ass. 2, B-, 4 November 1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Duke Ellington, June 1994; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Elaine Todd, Chief Justice Burber S. African Writers with Lama Students, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - ESP not prl, 1973-1974; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - ESP Pairs, 1976, 1979; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Eva and Terry, 1978; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Eva and Terry, Donato Donna Morrison, July 1978; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Felix Week #1 Aziz in Shop, March 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Francesca/Perrice Intro?, January 1991; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Garfield, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Gerri Truskwoki's Art Work, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Gloria Keys (200), A-, 17 October 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - Gloria Keys Music, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 21)
    - Goats (Rusty, Blackie, Bonnie, Bella, Baby Ray), 1979; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 22)
    - Goats, Sharon, Karate Tournament, Andre Lorde, Cristina, 1 March 1979; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 23)
    - Graduation - Rejects, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 24)
    - Graduation Senior Visual Arts Exhibit, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 41, Folder 25)
    - Graduation Slide Show, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Harper's Ferry David's Farm - Rejects Lit. Arts, 1987; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Heather Williams, B-, 1990; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Horse Show, Margaret Lee and Anna, 1979; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Imhotep's Jewelry, August 1980; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - India C. Gullatt, 1966; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Intro 2nd Advisory - Photos of Teddy and Tore, January 1992; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Intro to Arts - Slides by Shanea Coates, Charles Wilkes, and Sean Simmons, 1987-1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Intro to the Arts by Renee Moore, Shane Coates, Cal Dade, Kyle Dade, and Charlotte Hays, 1987-1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Jan's Furniture, 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Jenelle Chambers, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Johanna's Rejects, 1979; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Jon Seder Ambience, B+, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Kirk Evans, 30 October 1986; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Kirk Evans - Thai Dancers, 18 September; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - Kitchen still lifes with strobe, lieca with apple, girl with hat in Volkswagon, B.B. in hat, Macro guitar, Blackie, 1976; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Krystal Brown Ass. #1 - Photojournalism, B- 1:00-2:30, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 16)
    - Krystal Brown Ass. 3 - Photojournalism 1:00, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 17)
    - LaJuanda Meyers, 1988; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 18)
    - LaJuanda Myers, n.d., undated; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 19)
    - LaJuanda Myers Photojournalism III/ Senior Slides, October 1989; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - LaTanya Wright, C+, 1986-1994; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - Leigh and Michelle - Hight!!, November 1978; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - Lena and Miosia, 1981; Series 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Leonard Worley Pan Africa Day, February 1990; SEries 6 Subseries 4 (Box 42, Folder 24)